A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1947-1951 FA759
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1947
  - United States of America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 02.1947/200.D
    - United States, 1947 (Box 374, Folder 2526)
  - United States of America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/200.E
    - United States, 1947 (Box 374, Folder 2526)
  - United States of America - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/200.R
    - United States, 1947 (Box 374, Folder 2527)
  - United States of America - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/200.S
    - United States - (A-R), 1947 (Box 375, Folder 2528)
    - United States - Social Science Research Council (A-Z), 1947 (Box 375, Folder 2529)
    - United States - University of Michigan: Survey Research Center, 1947 (Box 375, Folder 2530)
  - Alaska, 1947; 02.1947/202
    - Alaska, 1947 (Box 375, Folder 2531)
  - California, 1947; 02.1947/205
    - California - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 375, Folder 2531)
    - California - University of California (A-Z), 1947 (Box 375, Folder 2532)
    - California, 1947 (Box 375, Folder 2533)
    - California, 1947 (Box 375, Folder 2533)
    - California, 1947 (Box 375, Folder 2534)
  - California - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/205.A
    - California, 1947 (Box 375, Folder 2533)
  - California - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/205.R
    - California, 1947 (Box 375, Folder 2533)
  - California - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/205.S
    - California, 1947 (Box 375, Folder 2534)
  - Colorado - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/207.A
    - Colorado, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2535)
  - Colorado - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/207.R
    - Colorado, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2535)
  - Colorado - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/207.S
    - Colorado, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2535)
  - Florida, 1947; 02.1947/211
    - Florida, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2535)
  - Georgia, 1947; 02.1947/212
    - Georgia, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2535)
  - Hawaii, 1947; 02.1947/214
    - Hawaii, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2535)
  - Illinois, 1947; 02.1947/216
    - Illinois - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2536)
    - Illinois - University of Chicago (A-T), 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2537)
    - Illinois - University of Chicago (U-Z), 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2538)
  - Illinois - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 02.1947/216.D
    - Illinois, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2538)
  - Illinois - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/216.R
    - Illinois, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2538)
  - Indiana, 1947; 02.1947/217
    - Indiana, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2539)
  - Kentucky, 1947; 02.1947/220
    - Kentucky, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2539)
  - Massachusetts, 1947; 02.1947/224
    - Massachusetts, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2539)
  - Massachusetts - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/224.A
    - Massachusetts, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2539)
  - Michigan, 1947; 02.1947/225
    - Michigan, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2540)
  - Mississippi, 1947; 02.1947/227
    - Mississippi, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2540)
  - North Carolina, 1947; 02.1947/236
    - North Carolina, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2540)
  - Ohio, 1947; 02.1947/238
    - Ohio, 1947 (Box 376, Folder 2540)
  - Pennsylvania, 1947; 02.1947/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2541)
  - Phillipines, 1947; 02.1947/242
    - Philippines, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2542)
  - Phillipines - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/242.E
    - Philippines, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2543)
  - Phillipines - Malaria, 1947; 02.1947/242.I
    - Philippines, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2543)
  - Phillipines - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/242.R
    - Philippines, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2543)
    - Philippines - Libraries - Reports, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2544)
  - Puerto Rico, 1947; 02.1947/243
    - Puerto Rico, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2545)
  - Rhode Island, 1947; 02.1947/244
    - Rhode Island, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2545)
  - South Carolina, 1947; 02.1947/246
    - South Carolina, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2545)
  - Tennessee, 1947; 02.1947/248
    - Tennessee, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2545)
  - Virginia, 1947; 02.1947/252
    - Virginia, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2546)
  - Virginia - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/252.A
    - Virginia, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2546)
  - Washington, 1947; 02.1947/253
    - Washington, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2546)
  - Wisconsin, 1947; 02.1947/255
    - Wisconsin, 1947 (Box 377, Folder 2546)
  - South America, 1947; 02.1947/300
    - South America - Administration, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2547)
  - South America, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2549)
    - South America - Administration, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2548)
  - South America - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/300.A
    - South America, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2549)
  - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 02.1947/300.D
    - South America, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2549)
  - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/300.E
    - South America, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2549)
  - Argentina, 1947; 02.1947/301
    - Argentina, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2550)
    - Argentina, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2551)
  - Bolivia, 1947; 02.1947/303
    - Bolivia, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2551)
  - Brazil, 1947; 02.1947/305
    - Brazil, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2552)
  - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/305.E
    - Brazil, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2553)
  - Brazil - Malaria, 1947; 02.1947/305.I
    - Brazil, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2553)
  - Brazil - Yellow Fever, 1947; 02.1947/305.O
    - Brazil, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2553)
  - Brazil - Tuberculosis, 1947; 02.1947/305.T
    - Brazil, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 2553)
  - Chile, 1947; 02.1947/309
    - Chile, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2554)
  - Chile - Nursing, 1947; 02.1947/309.C
    - Chile, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2554)
  - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/309.E
    - Chile, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2554)
  - Colombia, 1947; 02.1947/311
    - Colombia, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2555)
  - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 02.1947/311.D
    - Colombia, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2555)
    - Colombia - National University of Colombia - (Agriculture), 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2556)
  - Costa Rica, 1947; 02.1947/313
    - Costa Rica, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Cuba, 1947; 02.1947/315
    - Cuba, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Ecuador, 1947; 02.1947/317
    - Ecuador, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Ecuador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/317.E
    - Ecuador, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Guatemala, 1947; 02.1947/319
    - Guatemala, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Guatemala - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/319.S
    - Guatemala, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Haiti, 1947; 02.1947/320
    - Haiti, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Honduras, 1947; 02.1947/321
    - Honduras, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Honduras - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 02.1947/321.D
    - Honduras, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2557)
  - Mexico, 1947; 02.1947/323
    - Mexico - Administration, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2558)
    - Mexico - (A-H), 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2559)
    - Mexico - (I-Z), 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2560)
  - Mexico - Public Health Education, 1947; 02.1947/323.L
    - Mexico, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2560)
  - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/323.R
    - Mexico, 1947 (Box 379, Folder 2560)
  - Nicaragua, 1947; 02.1947/325
    - Nicaragua, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2561)
  - Panama, 1947; 02.1947/327
    - Panama, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2561)
  - Panama - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/327.R
    - Panama, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2561)
  - Peru, 1947; 02.1947/331
    - Peru, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2561)
  - Peru - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/331.A
    - Peru, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2562)
  - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Award, 1947; 02.1947/331.E
    - Peru, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2562)
  - El Salvador, 1947; 02.1947/333
    - Salvador, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2562)
  - Dominican Republic, 1947; 02.1947/335
    - Dominican Republic, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2562)
  - Dominican Republic - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/335.E
    - Dominican Republic, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2562)
  - Uruguay, 1947; 02.1947/337
    - Uruguay, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2562)
  - Uruguay - Nursing, 1947; 02.1947/337.C
    - Uruguay, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2562)
  - Venezuela, 1947; 02.1947/339
    - Venezuela, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2563)
    - Venezuela, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2564)
  - Great Britain, 1947; 02.1947/400
    - Great Britain, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2565)
  - England, 1947; 02.1947/401
    - England (A-H), 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2565)
    - England (I-M), 1947 (Box 380, Folder 2566)
    - England (N-O), 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2567)
    - England - (P-U), 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2568)
    - England - (University A-Z), 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2569)
    - England - (W-Z), 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2570)
    - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2571)
  - England - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/401.A
    - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2571)
  - England - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 02.1947/401.D
    - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2571)
  - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/401.E
    - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2571)
  - England - Public Health Education, 1947; 02.1947/401.L
    - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2571)
  - England - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/401.R
    - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2571)
    - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2572)
  - England - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/401.S
    - England, 1947 (Box 381, Folder 2572)
  - Ireland, 1947; 02.1947/403
  - Ireland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/403.E
    - Ireland, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2573)
  - Scotland, 1947; 02.1947/405
    - Scotland, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2574)
  - Scotland - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/405.S
    - Scotland, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2574)
  - Wales, 1947; 02.1947/407
    - Wales, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2574)
  - Australia, 1947; 02.1947/410
    - Australia, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2575)
  - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/410.A
    - Australia, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2575)
  - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/410.E
    - Australia, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2575)
  - New Zealand, 1947; 02.1947/418
    - New Zealand, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2576)
  - New Zealand - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/418.A
    - New Zealand, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2576)
  - New Zealand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/418.E
    - New Zealand, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2576)
  - Caribbean Region, 1947; 02.1947/420
    - Caribbean Region - Administration, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2577)
    - Caribbean Region - Administration, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2578)
    - Caribbean Region, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2579)
  - British Guiana, 1947; 02.1947/423
    - British Guiana, 1947 (Box 382, Folder 2579)
  - Canada, 1947; 02.1947/427
    - Canada - (Administration), 1947 (Box 383, Folder 2580)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 383, Folder 2581)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 383, Folder 2582)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 383, Folder 2583)
    - Canada - (University: A-Z), 1947 (Box 383, Folder 2584)
  - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/427.A
    - Canada - (A-U), 1947 (Box 383, Folder 2585)
    - University of British Columbia, 1947 (Box 383, Folder 2586)
  - Canada - (U-Z), 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2587)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1947; 02.1947/427.C
      - Canada, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2588)
  - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/427.E
    - Canada, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2588)
  - Canada - Public Health Demonstrations, 1947; 02.1947/427.J
    - Canada, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2588)
  - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/427.R
    - Canada, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2588)
  - Canada - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/427.S
    - Canada, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2588)
  - West Indies, 1947; 02.1947/431
    - British West Indies, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2589)
  - Bermuda, 1947; 02.1947/437
    - Bermuda, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2589)
  - Bermuda - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/437.E
    - Bermuda, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2589)
  - Trinidad, 1947; 02.1947/451
    - Trinidad, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2589)
  - Sri Lanka, 1947; 02.1947/462
  - Sri Lanka - Nursing, 1947; 02.1947/462.C
    - Sri Lanka, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2589)
  - India, 1947; 02.1947/464
    - India - Administration, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2590)
    - India - (A-R), 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2591)
    - India - Sankaran, C., 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2592)
    - India - (S-Z), 1947 (Box 384, Folder 2593)
  - India - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/464.A
    - India, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2594)
  - India - Nursing, 1947; 02.1947/464.C
    - India, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2594)
  - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/464.E
    - India - Government Fellows - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2595)
    - India - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2596)
  - India - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/464.R
    - India, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2597)
  - India - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/464.S
    - India, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2597)
  - Pakistan, 1947; 02.1947/465
  - Pakistan - Nursing, 1947; 02.1947/465.C
    - Pakistan, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Pakistan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/465.E
    - Pakistan, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Burma, 1947; 02.1947/468
    - Burma, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Burma - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/468.A
    - Burma, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Burma - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/468.R
    - Burma, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Iraq, 1947; 02.1947/470
    - Iraq, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Malaysia, 1947; 02.1947/473
    - Malaysia, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Africa, 1947; 02.1947/475
    - Africa, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Africa - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/475.R
    - Africa, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2598)
  - Ethiopia, 1947; 02.1947/477
  - Egypt, 1947; 02.1947/485
    - Egypt - Administration, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2599)
    - Egypt - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2600)
  - South Africa, 1947; 02.1947/487
    - South Africa, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2600)
  - South Africa - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/487.S
    - South Africa, 1947 (Box 385, Folder 2600)
  - France, 1947; 02.1947/500
    - France - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2601)
    - France - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2602)
    - France - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2603)
  - France - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/500.A
    - France, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2604)
  - France - Nursing, 1947; 02.1947/500.C
    - France, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2604)
  - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/500.E
    - France, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2604)
  - France - Declinations, 1947; 02.1947/500.F
    - France, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2604)
  - France - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/500.R
    - France, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2604)
  - Vietnam, 1947; 02.1947/509
    - Vietnam, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2605)
  - Asia, 1947; 02.1947/600
    - Asia, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2605)
  - Asia - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/600.R
    - Asia, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2605)
  - China, 1947; 02.1947/601
    - China - Administration, 1947 (Box 386, Folder 2606)
    - China - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2607)
    - China - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2608)
    - China - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2609)
  - China - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/601.A
    - China, 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2610)
  - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/601.E
    - China, 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2610)
  - China - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/601.R
    - China, 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2610)
  - Taiwan, 1947; 02.1947/605
  - Taiwan - Nursing, 1947; 02.1947/605.C
    - Taiwan, 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2611)
  - Japan, 1947; 02.1947/609
    - Japan - (A-J), 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2611)
    - Japan - (K-Z), 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2612)
  - Japan - Nursing, 1947; 02.1947/609.C
    - Japan, 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2612)
  - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Award, 1947; 02.1947/609.E
    - Japan, 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2612)
  - Japan - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/609.S
    - Japan, 1947 (Box 387, Folder 2612)
    - EVANS-1 Evans, Roger F. "Japan-Korea Diary", 1947 (Box 562, Folder 3832)
      General note
      Stack Material
  - Korea, 1947; 02.1947/613
    - Korea, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2613)
  - Korea - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/613.A
    - Korea, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2613)
  - Korea - Nursing, 1947; 02.1947/613.C
    - Korea, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2613)
  - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/613.E
    - Korea, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2613)
  - Korea - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/613.R
    - Korea, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2613)
  - Korea - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/613.S
    - Korea, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2613)
  - Thailand, 1947; 02.1947/617
  - Thailand - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/617.A
    - Thailand, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2613)
  - Holland, 1947; 02.1947/650
    - Netherlands - (A-T), 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2614)
    - Netherlands - (U-Z), 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2615)
  - Holland - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/650.A
    - Netherlands, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2615)
  - Holland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/650.E
    - Netherlands, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2615)
  - Holland - Health Services, 1947; 02.1947/650.K
    - Netherlands, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2615)
    - LOG-2 Logan, John A. "Recommendations for the Promotion of Sanitary Engineering in the Netherlands", 1947 (Box 562, Folder 3833)
  - Holland - Public Health Education, 1947; 02.1947/650.L
    - Netherlands, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2615)
  - Holland - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/650.R
    - Netherlands, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2615)
  - Indonesia, 1947; 02.1947/655
    - Indonesia, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2616)
  - Sumatra, 1947; 02.1947/657
    - Sumatra, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2616)
  - Europe, 1947; 02.1947/700
    - Europe, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2616)
    - LEAV-1 Leavall, Hugh R. "England and Scandinavia Diary", 1947 (Box 562, Folder 3834)
  - Ethiopia, 1947; 02.1947/701
    - Ethiopia, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2617)
  - Afghanistan, 1947; 02.1947/703
    - Afghanistan, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2617)
  - Austria, 1947; 02.1947/705
    - Austria, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2617)
  - Austria - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/705.A
    - Austria, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2617)
  - Austria - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/705.R
    - Austria, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2617)
  - Austria - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/705.S
    - Austria, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2617)
  - Austria - Tuberculosis, 1947; 02.1947/705.T
    - Austria, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2617)
  - Belgium, 1947; 02.1947/707
    - Belgium, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2618)
  - Belgium - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/707.R
    - Belgium, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2618)
  - Belgium - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/707.S
    - Belgium, 1947 (Box 388, Folder 2618)
  - Yugoslavia, 1947; 02.1947/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2619)
  - Yugoslavia - Nursing, 1947; 02.1947/710.C
    - Yugoslavia, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2619)
  - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/710.E
    - Yugoslavia, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2619)
  - Yugoslavia - Public Health Education, 1947; 02.1947/710.L
    - Yugoslavia, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2619)
  - Bulgaria, 1947; 02.1947/711
    - Bulgaria, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2619)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1947; 02.1947/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2620)
    - Czechoslovakia, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2621)
  - Denmark, 1947; 02.1947/713
    - Denmark, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2622)
  - Denmark - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/713.A
    - Denmark, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2622)
  - Denmark - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 02.1947/713.D
  - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/713.E
    - Denmark, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2622)
  - Denmark, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2622)
  - Denmark - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/713.R
    - Denmark, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2622)
  - Germany, 1947; 02.1947/717
    - Germany - (A-P), 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2623)
    - Germany - (A-P), 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2624)
    - Germany - Publications, 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2625)
    - Germany - (R-T), 1947 (Box 389, Folder 2626)
    - Germany - (U-Z), 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2627)
  - Germany - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/717.A
    - Germany, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2628)
  - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 02.1947/717.D
    - Germany, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2628)
  - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/717.E
    - Germany, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2628)
  - Germany - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/717.R
    - Germany, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2628)
    - Press Personnel (1) - PP, 1947 (Box 563, Folder 3835)
    - Press Personnel (1) - PP, 1947 (Box 563, Folder 3836)
  - Germany - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/717.S
    - Germany, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2628)
  - Tanzania, 1947; 02.1947/723
    - Tanzania, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2629)
  - Greece, 1947; 02.1947/749
    - Greece, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2629)
  - Greece - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 02.1947/749.D
    - Greece, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2629)
  - Greece - Malaria, 1947; 02.1947/749.I
    - Greece, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2629)
  - Greece - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/749.S
    - Greece, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2629)
  - Hungary, 1947; 02.1947/750
    - Hungary - (A-Z), 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2630)
  - Hungary - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1947; 02.1947/750.D
    - Hungary, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2631)
  - Hungary - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/750.E
    - Hungary, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2631)
  - Hungary - Malaria, 1947; 02.1947/750.I
    - Hungary, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2631)
  - Hungary - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/750.R
    - Hungary, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2631)
  - Italy, 1947; 02.1947/751
    - Italy, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2632)
  - Italy - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/751.A
    - Italy, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2633)
  - Italy - Nursing, 1947; 02.1947/751.C
    - Italy, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2633)
  - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/751.E
    - Italy, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2633)
  - Italy - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/751.R
    - Italy, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2633)
  - Italy - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/751.S
    - Italy, 1947 (Box 390, Folder 2633)
  - Norway, 1947; 02.1947/767
    - Norway, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2634)
  - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/767.E
    - Norway, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2634)
  - Norway - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/767.R
    - Norway, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2634)
  - Norway - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/767.S
    - Norway, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2634)
  - Iran, 1947; 02.1947/771
    - Iran, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2635)
  - Iran - Nursing, 1947; 02.1947/771.C
    - Iran, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2635)
  - Portugal, 1947; 02.1947/773
    - Portugal, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2635)
  - Portugal - Nursing, 1947; 02.1947/773.C
    - Portugal, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2635)
  - Romania, 1947; 02.1947/783
    - Romania, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2635)
  - Ukraine, 1947; 02.1947/784
    - Ukraine, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2635)
  - Russia, 1947; 02.1947/785
    - USSR, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2636)
  - Russia - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/785.A
    - USSR, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2636)
  - Russia - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/785.R
    - USSR, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2636)
  - Russia - Social Services, 1947; 02.1947/785.S
    - USSR, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2636)
  - Latvia, 1947; 02.1947/786
    - Latvia, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2637)
  - Finland, 1947; 02.1947/787
    - Finland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2637)